Guide to the Kristine Stiles Collection, 1900-[ongoing] RL.01254
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Kristine Stiles collection
1900-ongoing
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Stiles, Kristine
RL.01254
200 Linear Feet 132,000 Items
0.83 Gigabytes
Kristine Stiles is the France Family Professor of Art, Art History & Visual Studies. Her main field of research is contemporary art with a focus on experimental practices, as well as representations of destruction, violence and trauma in art. The collection includes several different series, including Stiles' personal and family papers, projects and writings, correspondence, photographs, and an artist archive documenting her correspondence and relationships with hundreds of contemporary modern artists from around the world. This archive has been sorted by each artist's last name and includes such artists as Chris Burden, Lynn Hershman, Allan Kaprow, Gustav Metzger, John Latham, Jean-Jacques Lebel, Yoko Ono, Raphael Montañez Ortiz, Dan and Lia Perjovschi, Carolee Schneemann, Wolf Vostell and many more.
Access Restrictions
Collection is restricted. Researchers must have permission from Kristine Stiles to use this material.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48 hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Provenance
The Kristine Stiles Collection was received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a gift in 2009, 2010, and 2012.
Biographical Note
Kristine Stiles is a professor of Art and Art History at Duke University. Her main field of research is contemporary art with a focus on performance art and other interdisciplinary experimental art practices. Her research is especially concerned with global representations of violence, trauma, and destruction.
Collection Overview
The collection includes several different series, including Stiles' personal and family papers; projects and writings; correspondence; photographs; and an artist archive documenting her correspondence and relationship with over 60 different contemporary and modern artists from around the world.
The Personal and Family Papers series includes scrapbooks, photographs, and albums of Stiles family history, dating back to the early 20th century and including much of her extended family. The majority of the series consists of family correspondence between Stiles and her parents, siblings, ex-husbands, and other extended family members. Also included are Stiles' diaries, poetry, schoolwork, and other personal papers.
The Perjovschi Project series largely relates to the States of Mind exhibit that Stiles curated for the Nasher Museum of Art in 2007, highlighting the art of Dan and Lia Perjovschi. The couple's relationship with Stiles is also documented in this series, which includes correspondence between them, as well as original art, books sent to her, and details about their earlier visits to Duke and Stiles' visits to Romania in the 1990s.
The Artist Archive series represents the bulk of the collection, and is Stiles' archive of correspondence, documentation, interviews, and other interactions with over 60 modern and contemporary artists from around the world. This series frequently focuses on the Destruction in Art Symposium (DIAS), and many of the original participants are represented here. Artists and groups have been arranged in alphabetical order, but on occasion, multiple artists are in the same box.
The Photographs series includes a wide range of items, including personal and family photographs of Stiles and her family, photographs taken by Stiles during her trips around the world, and photographs by other people of the DIAS movement. Also included are some scrapbooks and other fragile materials from Stiles' childhood.
The Writings and Projects series is focused largely on Stiles' research and artwork, and dates from her early childhood through recent research as a professor at Duke. Included are details and ephemera from her performance art and exhibitions, such as the Romeo Drawing Book and cassette tapes from her Questions installation. Also contains her Ph.D. dissertation.
Journals and Magazines is a series that includes zines, newsletters, and other periodicals that Stiles collected throughout her life. Many of these publications lasted only 1 or 2 issues. A notable portion of this series is the Apexart.org publications and the DIA Center for the Arts brochures, both of which include item-level description below.
The Name Files series is another large series that includes small amounts of correspondence, brochures, clippings, and communications from a variety of artists, family members, colleagues, and galleries. This series does not include Stiles' communications with artists represented in the Artist Archive series. It is foldered alphabetically.
The Audiovisual Materials series includes videotapes and recordings collected by Stiles from various artists promoting their work.
Other Artist Writings includes articles and writings by people other than Stiles; she collected them in the course of her research.
Posters and Oversize Materials include large items from a variety of sources in the collection. Frequently this series deals with materials that have been pulled from other series for preservation and housing.
Conditions Governing Access
Electronic records in this collection have been migrated to a library server and digital use copies can only be accessed onsite in the Rubenstein Library Reading Room.
Performance art; Art, Modern -- 20th century; Art, Modern -- 21st century; Photography, Artistic; Stiles, Kristine; Perjovschi, Lia, 1961-; Fluxus (Group of artists); Duke University. Dept. of Art; Perjovschi, Dan; Ortiz, Raphael Montanez; Metzger, Gustav; Lebel, Jean Jacques
- Personal and Family Papers, 20 boxes
  Scope and Contents note
  Family correspondence, diaries, address books, family history and memoirs, correspondence with ex-husbands, scrapbooks, photographs, poetry, and dresses.
  - Schoolwork, 1960s-1970s (3 folders) (Box 1)
  - Miscellaneous papers, including travel grant applications and resumes, 1970s (Box 1)
  - Dartington College of Arts Honorary Ph.D. (Box 1)
  - VIP letters from Duke officials (Box 1)
  - Shay playbill (Stiles' favorite play) (Box 1)
  - Stiles Poetry, 1970s-1980s (3 folders) (Box 1)
  - Paul G. Dolan (father) correspondence with Kristine, 1950s-1992 (2 folders) (Box 1)
  - Stephen R. Dolan correspondence, 1980s-2000s (2 folders) (Box 1)
  - Randolph Stiles correspondence, 1960s-2009 (Box 1)
  - Randolph Stiles photo albums (1970s) (Box 2)
  - Wedding album (Box 2)
  - Correspondence (Box 2)
  - Scrapbooks and diaries, 1960s-1970s (Box 2)
  - Frederick Rand Rogers: Educational Provocateur, dissertation by Garfield Gary Pennington, 1972 (Box 3)
  - Frederick Rand Rogers: Educational Provocateur, article, 1981 (Box 3)
  - The Descendants of Col. Andrew Jackson: Lane and Frances Vivian Brooking Lane, Hillyer Rudisill III, 1994 (Box 3)
  - Interview with James A. Wylie, June 1967 (Box 3)
  - Photo album of great-grandfathers John Rankin Rogers and George Spalitin Easterday (Box 3)
  - Family photographs: Father, mother, grandparents, ex-husbands, 1960s-2000s (Box 4)
  - Grandmother's childhood (Beatrice Easterday Rogers) (3 folders) (Box 4)
  - Scrapbook: Our Ancestors by Katherine Haller Rogers Dolan (mother) (2 folders) (Box 4)
  - Family materials and memorabilia, 1950s-2000s (Box 4)
  - Family correspondence, 1960s-1990s (Box 4)
  - Family correspondence, 1960s-1990s (Box 5)
  - Mother's death, 2001 (Box 5)
  - Mother's writings (Box 5)
  - Diaries, 1960s-1980s (Box 5)
  - Diaries and address books, 1960s-1980s (Box 6)
  - Dress worn in Missouri Miss Universe contest when Kristine won Miss Congeniality (Box 7)
  - Red dress: worn to parties that Kristine attended with Sherman Fleming and in performance Red Bed Great Cave (Box 8)
  - Black dress: worn in performance with Sherman Fleming, Western History… (Box 8)
  - Family history and memoirs (3 folders) (Box 9)
  - Katherine Dolan stroke, 1980 (Box 9)
  - Silence memoir, by Katherine Dolan (Box 9)
  - Memories and then some, draft by Katherine Dolan (Box 9)
  - Family correspondence, 1990s (Box 9)
  - Correspondence with Paul Gregory Dolan Jr., older brother, 1980s-2000s (3 folders) (Box 10)
  - Johanna Jogie S. Dolan, sister in law (2 folders) (Box 10)
  - Fred Dolan, nephew (1 folder) (Box 10)
  - Bettina Dolan, niece (1 folder) (Box 10)
  - Kevin Dolan, nephew (1 folder) (Box 10)
  - Stiles' wedding to Edward A. Shanken, 1996 July 14: correspondence, photos, planning info, guest book (Box 11)
  - Katherine Victoria Dolan Tierney correspondence (Box 11)
  - Grace Fain and Thomas Dolan correspondence (Box 11)
  - Jain McClain Dolan correspondence (Box 11)
  - Luke Utterback correspondence (Box 11)
  - Stephanie Joy Spruill Cheves correspondence (Box 11)
  - Constance Sue Dolan correspondence (Box 12)
  - Sondra Spruil Triblehorn correspondence (Box 12)
  - Sandra Spruill Cooper correspondence (Box 12)
  - Godchildren correspondence (Box 12)
  - Mark D. Hasencamp (second husband), 1970s-2000s (Box 12)
  - Mark Hasencamp: The First Washington Book (diary) (Box 13)
  - Mark Hasencamp diaries (Box 13)
  - Mark Hasencamp correspondence, 1980s-2000s (Box 13)
  - Edward A. Shanken (third husband) correspondence, drawings, and photographs, 1994-2003 (Box 14)
  - Edward A. Shanken correspondence, travel diary, A Cut Up Book, photographs, other trinkets and ephemera, 1995-2008 (Box 15)
  - Edward A. Shanken correspondence, vacation photographs, 1990s (Box 16)
  - Edward A. Shanken correspondence, cards, Stiles' poetry (Box 17)
  - Marion Lane Rogers Sr. correspondence, 2000s (Box 18)
  - Frederick Rand Rogers correspondence, 1965-1971 (Box 18, Box 214)
  - Marion Lane Rogers Sr. essay, 1977 (Box 18)
  - Acorn Days book by Marion Lane Rogers Sr., 1990 (Box 18)
  - San Francisco DVD, 1967-1968 (Box 18)
  - Marion Lane Rogers Sr. correspondence and photographs (Box 19)
  - Marion Lane Rogers correspondence, 2009-2011 (Box 203)
  - Marion Lane Rogers professional materials (Box 203)
  - Beatrice Easterday family history (Box 203)
  - Docs Valen Te No (Eryk), Stiles' horse (Box 203, Box 212)
  - LPs of Stiles' high school choir (Box 203)
  - Family correspondence, including letters from Frederick Rand Rogers to Marion Lane Rogers, Sr., 1967-1968 (Box 212)
  - Family correspondence, between Frederick Rand Rogers, Katherine Rogers Dolan, and Kristine Dolan Stiles, 1969 and undated (Box 212)
  - "Basic Human Engineering," by Frederick Rand Rogers, 1961 (Box 212)
  - Stephen R. Dolan correspondence, 2012-2015 (Box 212)
  - Marion Lane Rogers Sr. correspondence, 2000s (Box 214)
  - Cathy Strack, Pilates, cc: Marion Lane Rogers, Sr., 2013 (Box 214)
  - Edward A. Shanken correspondence, 2009 (Box 214)
  - Marion Lane Jones, Jr. correspondence, 2012-2015 (Box 215)
  - Frederick Rand Rogers' correspondence to Marion Lane Rogers, Sr., 1965-1966 (Box 215)
  - Marion Lane Rogers, Jr. correspondence, 2012-2015 (Box 215)
  - Strack, Cathy: Pilates, cc: Marion Lane Rogers, Jr. (Box 215)
  - Edward A. Shanken correspondence, 2009 (Box 215)
- Perjovschi Project, 10 boxes
  Materials from Kristine Stiles' correspondence and interactions with close friends Dan and Lia Perjovschi, Romanian artists. She arranged for them to be visiting professors at Duke in 1997, and also curated an exhibit of their art, States of Mind, at the Nasher Museum of Art in 2007.
  Arrangement note
  Oversize materials have been removed to the Oversize Posters series. See Box 194 and Oversize Folder 5.
  - States of Mind: Lia and Dan Perjovschi, 2007-2008 exhibit binder (2 folders) (Box 20)
  - Perjovschi exhibit images binder (with CDs) (5 folders) (Box 20)
  - Perjovschi exhibit edits to the script (4 folders) (Box 20)
  - Perjovschi exhibit edits (Box 21-22)
  - Perjovschi exhibit checklist: (Box 23)
    - Text edits (Box 23)
    - Bibliography (Box 23)
    - Notes and correspondence (3 folders) (Box 23)
    - Book (Box 23)
    - Materials (Box 23)
    - CDs (Box 23)
  - Nasher exhibit, Fall 2007 (Box 24)
  - Notes by Kristine Stiles on Dan and Lia Perjovschi (Box 24)
  - Duke Magazine and other publications (Box 24)
  - Photographs of performances (Box 24)
  - Contemporary Art from Romania, 1997 (Box 24)
  - Prints and photographs of publications of Dan's drawings (Box 24)
  - Publications (Box 24)
  - Artist proof, 1995 (Box 24)
  - Drawing course artwork, 1997 (Box 24)
  - Revista 22 newspapers (created by Dan Perjovschi), 1992-2000s (Box 25)
  - Flyers and postcards for exhibits (Box 25)
  - International Visitors Program, 1994 (Box 25)
  - 2 CDs, 1 audiocassette (Box 25)
  - Original art by Dan and Lia Perjovschi (Box 26)
  - Catalogs and publications of their art (Box 26)
  - Correspondence between the Perjovschis and Stiles, 2006-2009 (Box 27)
  - Dan Perjovschi Quimpering (2 copies), 2005 (Box 27)
  - Postcards from America (2 copies) (Box 27)
  - Zoom: Performance, Installation, and Video Art, 1997 (Duke) (Box 27)
  - Flyers, newsletters, photographs, postcards, prints (Box 27)
  - Notepad with Lia's notes (Box 27)
  - Correspondence between the Perjovschis and Stiles, 1995-2000s (Box 28)
  - ARTs publication, 1991 (Box 28)
  - Notes and articles by Stiles about the Perjovschis (Box 28)
  - Photocopies of pictures of shows (Box 28)
  - 5 microcassettes, 1 CD-ROM, 16 tapes, 1990s-2000s (Box 28)
  - 1 box of slides (Box 28)
  - Bucharest University student papers (Box 29)
  - Miscellaneous artwork (Box 29)
  - Notes and correspondence, 1980s-2000s (Box 29)
  - Photographs, 1995, 1998, 2007 (Box 29)
  - 1 linen bag with iron-on photographs and art (Box 29)
  - Correspondence, 1994-2011 (Box 29)
- Artist Archive, 101 boxes
  Stiles maintained an archive of her correspondence and interactions with artists from around the world. She met many of them through her research on the art of destruction and trauma. The majority of this material is correspondence between the artists and Stiles. Boxes will also often include postcards and gallery catalogs advertising performances or shows, as well as examples of original art, memorabilia from the artists' work or activities, books or printed materials, and personalized gifts for Stiles.
  Materials are listed below in alphabetical order by artist or group name, occasionally putting boxes out of sequential order. Some boxes include more than one artist, meaning that some box numbers have been repeated as each artist is listed in their place alphabetically.
  - Art and Language (England) (Box 30)
    - Correspondence, 2000s (Box 30)
    - Duke Seminar publicity, including signed posters (Box 30)
    - 10 audiocassettes of Duke Seminar, 2002 (Box 30)
  - Arte Destructivo (Argentina) (Box 31)
    Argentinean Art Group, 1961; included artists Kenneth Kemble, Jorge López Anaya, Luis Alberto Wells, Jorge Roiger, Silvia Torras, Enrique Barilari, Antonio Segui.
    - Destructive Art, by Kenneth Kemble (translated from Spanish) (Box 31)
    - 4 audiocassette tapes (Box 31)
    - Correspondence, 1980s (Box 31)
    - Catalogs (Box 31)
  - Ascott, Roy (England) (Box 32)
    - Correspondence, 1990s (Box 32)
    - Telematic Embrace (book) (Box 32)
    - 33 RPM record, Groundcourse, Year Two, 1972 (Box 32)
    - Gallery catalogs and brochures (Box 32)
  - Auman, Graham (North Carolina, USA) (Box 33)
    - Artists Show posters and advertisements (Box 33)
    - 1 tshirt (Box 33)
    - Artist Hanging, 1994 (Box 33)
    - Correspondence (Box 33)
  - Aya and Gal Middle East (Israel) (Box 85)
    - Original artwork (Box 85)
    - Correspondence (Box 85)
    - Pamphlets and brochures (Box 85)
  - Bhagat, Alexis (Box 215)
  - Bitzan, Ion (Romania) (Box 85)
    - Correspondence (Box 85)
    - Catalogs, including "Ion Bitzan's Desire" essay by Stiles (Box 85)
  - Bonk, Ecke (Germany) (Box 34)
    - Books:
      - A Prima Zeichen, Oktober 1980 (Box 34)
      - Im Zeichenraum/Ecke Bonk/Edition Ricochet/FV (Box 34)
      - For Bettina Fr. Kristine, 1979 (Box 34)
    - Correspondence, 1970s-2009 (Box 34)
    - 1 cassette tape (Box 34)
    - Correspondence, 1970s-1980s (Box 35)
    - Art show announcements (Box 35)
    - Oversize original art (Box 35)
    - Offene Handlungsfelder (Box 36)
    - Posters and postcards for shows (Box 36)
    - Handbuch Kunst Wien, 1981 (Box 36)
    - Catalogs (Box 36)
    - Correspondence (Box 36)
    - Gott Vater book (Box 36)
    - Tumult 7 (Box 36)
  - Braila, Pavel (Moldovia) (Box 85)
    - "Shoes for Europe" poster (Box 85)
    - Correspondence (Box 85)
  - Bratescu, Geta (Romania) (Box 85)
    - Biography and bibliography (Box 85)
    - Brochures (Box 85)
    - Annotated photocopies of exhibitions and notes (Box 85)
  - Burden, Chris (USA) (Box 37)
    - Correspondence (Box 37)
    - CD with Nancy Rubin label (Box 37)
    - 7 audiocassettes of taped interviews (Box 37)
    - Catalogs and programs for art shows (Box 37)
    - Press and articles (Box 37)
  - Cohen-Gan, Pinchas (Israel) (Box 38)
    - Art and Science Project, 1973 (Box 38)
    - Art as Mathematical Reality, 1982 (Box 38)
    - Critical Art, Hermeneutic Model, 1988 (Box 38)
    - Definition of Art and the Location of an Artwork (AICS), 1977 (Box 38)
    - Concrete Art in the Expanded Field (Box 38)
    - Correspondence (Box 38)
    - Slides (Box 38)
    - 6 audiocassettes of taped interviews (Box 38)
  - Conner, Bruce (USA) (Box 39)
    Oversize materials have been removed to the Oversize Posters series. See Box 195.
    - I am Bruce Conner buttons (3) (Box 39)
    - 1 t-shirt: Rat Bastard, 2000 (Box 39)
    - Art gallery advertisements, flyers, catalogs, and newspaper articles (Box 39)
    - Correspondence, 1970s-1990s (Box 39)
    - Correspondence (Box 40)
    - Advertisements, catalogs, and flyers (Box 40)
    - Cassette tape (Box 40)
    - Slides and photographs (Box 40)
    - Angels exhibit information (Box 40)
    - News clippings (Box 40)
    - Damage magazine (on newsprint), 1979-1980 (three issues) (Box 193)
    - Search and Destroy magazine, no. 4 and 6, 1977 and 1978 (Box 193)
    - RE-Search magazine, no. 1 and no. 2 (Box 193)
    - Bumper sticker, 1972 B.C. (Box 193)
    - Posters and advertisements for shows or exhibits (Box 193)
      Scope and Contents
      Based on 2014 research by the Nasher Museum done in conjunction with the exhibit "Rauschenberg: Collecting & Connecting," Bruce Conner's campaign poster for Supervisor occurred in 1967, not 1972.
  - Conz, Francesco (Italy) (Box 41)
    - Correspondence, 1990s-2000s (Box 41)
    - Canvas prints by Bob Watts, 1987 (Box 41)
    - News clippings (Box 41)
  - Cottingham, Laura (USA) (Box 42)
    - Lesbians are so chic..., 1997 (Box 42)
    - How many bad feminists does it take to change a lightbulb? (Box 42)
    - Correspondence, 1990s-2000s (Box 42)
  - Davidson, Karen (USA) (Box 43)
    - Correspondence (Box 43)
    - Pont la Vue Press information (Box 43)
    - Photographs (Box 43)
    - Original art: Dangling Modifier, 1980 (men's dress collar with text) (Box 43)
  - Davies, Ivor (Wales) (Box 44)
    - 4 boxes of slides (Box 44)
    - 1 cassette of taped interview (Box 44)
  - Del Tredici, Robert (Canada) (Box 45)
    - Books:
      - The Nuclear Map of Canada Project (Box 45)
      - Floodgates of the Wonderworld (Box 45)
    - Correspondence, 1995-2000s (Box 45)
    - Drawings and prints from Moby Dick project (Box 45)
    - Nuclear bomb information and prints, including atomic bomb radiation reports and articles (Box 45)
  - Edelsztein, Sergio (Israel) (Box 98)
    - Resume (Box 98)
    - Correspondence, 1996-2008 (Box 98)
  - Esanu, Octaviu (Moldovia) (Box 98)
    - Correspondence, 1997-2002 (Box 98)
    - Catalogs and brochures (Box 98)
  - Fischer, Hervé (France; Montreal since the mid-1980s) (Box 46)
    Fischer materials also include oversize posters and newspapers. Please see the Oversize Posters and Materials Series, Box 179.
    - Correspondence, 1980s (Box 46)
    - Photographs (Box 46)
    - Printed materials and catalogs (Box 46)
    - Books and journals (Box 178)
      - Art et Communication Marginale, 1974 (Box 178)
      - Théorie de l'art sociologique, 1977 (Box 178)
      - Citoyens / Sculpteurs, 1980 (Box 178)
      - Cahier de l'Ecole Sociologique Interrogative No. 1 (March 1980) (Box 178)
      - Cahier de l'Ecole Sociologique Interrogative No. 3, Special Issue (1980) (Box 178)
      - L'Histoire de L'Art est Terminée, 1981 (Box 178)
      - L'oiseau-chat, 1983 (Box 178)
      - La calle, ?adónde llega?, 1984 (Box 178)
      - Le choc du numérique, 2001 (Box 178)
      - Le romantisme numérique, 2001 (Box 178)
  - Fleming, Sherman (USA) (Box 47-51)
    - Correspondence (Box 47-51)
    - Exhibits and performance materials (Box 47-51)
    - Photographs (Box 47-51)
    - Pictures (Box 47-51)
    - Ephemera, including a ring, a t-shirt, and a Jack Daniels bottle (Box 47-51)
    - Cassette tape (Box 47-51)
    - Original works of art (Box 47-51)
    - Journals (Box 47-51)
    - Ceramic object (Box 47-51)
  - Flynt, Henry (USA) (Box 52)
    - Writings and drafts (Box 52)
    - Transcribed interview with Stiles, 1989 (Box 52)
    - Correspondence, 1980s-1990s (Box 52)
    - Creep Theory materials (Box 52)
    - Fragments and Reconstructions from a Destroyed Oeuvre, 1959-1963 (Box 52)
    - Mutations of the Vanguard, 1990 (Box 52)
    - 1 button (Box 52)
    - 5 cassette tapes of talks, 1962-1990 (Box 52)
  - Gechtman, Gideon (Israel) (Box 98)
    - Correspondence (Box 98)
    - Audiocassettes (3) (Box 98)
    - Slides of show in Tel Aviv (Box 98)
    - Photographs of installations and artwork (Box 98)
    - Clippings (Box 98)
  - Goldstein, Zvi (Israel) (Box 98)
    - Correspondence, 1996-2011 (Box 98)
    - Catalogs and brochures (Box 98)
    - Notebook (Box 98)
  - Graur, Teodor (Romania) (Box 85)
    - Bibliography of works (Box 85)
    - Exhibition slides (Box 85)
    - Postcards (blank) of art (Box 85)
  - Grigorescu, Ion (Romania) (Box 85, Box 215)
    - Audiocassettes (3), dated 1996 (Box 85)
    - Correspondence, 1993-2009 (Box 85, Box 215)
    - Photocopies of photographs and texts about Grigorescu's work (Box 85)
  - Hansen, Al (USA) (Box 53)
    - 1 cassette tape (Box 53)
    - Correspondence with Bibbie Hansen (Box 53)
    - OK Harris art gallery materials (Box 53)
    - Photographs and slides (Box 53)
    - Photocopied articles (Box 53)
    - Beck materials and show information (Box 53)
    - Santa Monica Museum of Art catalog (Box 53)
    - Handwritten answers to Stiles questions about DIAS and other art in the 1980s (Box 53)
  - Hershman, Lynn (USA) (Box 54-56)
    - Correspondence (Box 54-56)
    - Exhibit publications (Box 54-56)
    - 2 cassette tapes of interviews (Box 54-56)
  - Hess, Nicole (Box 57)
    - Correspondence, 2000s (Box 57)
  - Higgins, Dick (USA) (Box 57)
    - Correspondence (Box 57)
  - Hillings, Valerie (Box 57)
    - Correspondence, 1990s-2000s (Box 57)
  - Jetwave (USA) (Box 58-60)
    San Francisco Alternative Exhibition Space, 1980-1983. Artists include Randy Hussong, Fredrica Drotos, J.C. Garrett, and Bruce Gluck.
    - Correspondence (Box 58-60)
    - 2 Artist books (Box 58-60)
    - Postcards and correspondence (Box 58-60)
    - Photographs (Box 58-60)
    - DROTOS folder (Box 58-60)
    - KO [Jetwave] unpublished book with inserts, 1982 (Box 58-60)
  - Kantor, Istvan (Hungary, b. 1949) (Box 189)
    - Future Species exhibition catalog with article on Kantor by Stiles, 2009 (Box 189)
    - Monty Cansin, July 8, 2007 (signed copy with drawings) (Box 189)